12frenz.com 2008-05-17

# 12Frenz Mobile Community

**Protecting your privacy is important to 12Frenz.  Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.**

**Table of Contents:**

  * [Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences ](http://th.12frenz.com/frenzwap/privacyPolicy.do#info)  

 **What This Privacy Policy Covers**  
This policy covers how 12Frenz treats personal information that 12Frenz collects and receives, including information related to your past use of 12Frenz products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that 12Frenz does not own or control, or to people that 12Frenz does not employ or manage.   

[[top]](http://th.12frenz.com/frenzwap/privacyPolicy.do#top)  

**Information Collection and Use  
General**

12Frenz collects personal information when you register with 12Frenz, when you use 12Frenz products or services, when you visit 12Frenz pages or the pages of certain 12Frenz partners, and when you enter promotions. 12Frenz may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, post code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. When you register with 12Frenz and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

12Frenz collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. 

12Frenz automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser and/or hand phone, including your IP address, 12Frenz cookie information, phone number and the page you request. 

12Frenz uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Children**  
When a child under age 13 attempts to register with 12Frenz, we ask the child to have a parent or guardian create a 12Frenz Family Account to obtain parental permission.  
12Frenz does not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission.  
12Frenz does not ask a child under age 13 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion.

[[top]](http://th.12frenz.com/frenzwap/privacyPolicy.do#top)

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

12Frenz does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with 12Frenz under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help 12Frenz communicate with you about offers from 12Frenz and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing 12Frenz to collect and use their child's information without consenting to 12Frenz sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of 12Frenz's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We transfer information about you if 12Frenz is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, 12Frenz will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

12Frenz displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 

12Frenz does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

12Frenz advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stopk brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

12Frenz works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. For more information regarding providers of products or services that you've requested please read our detailed reference links.

[[top]](http://th.12frenz.com/frenzwap/privacyPolicy.do#top)

**Cookies**  
12Frenz may set and access 12Frenz cookies on your computer. 

12Frenz lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to 12Frenz's cookies. 

12Frenz uses web beacons to access 12Frenz cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with 12Frenz products and services.

[[top]](http://th.12frenz.com/frenzwap/privacyPolicy.do#top)

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences  
General**  
You can edit your 12Frenz Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. 

New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the 12Frenz service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the 12Frenz Newsletter, that are considered part of your 12Frenz account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

You can delete your 12Frenz account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.   
****

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.

[[top]](http://th.12frenz.com/frenzwap/privacyPolicy.do#top)   

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

12Frenz may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your 12Frenz account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

[[top]](http://th.12frenz.com/frenzwap/privacyPolicy.do#top)
